{
    "subject": "resource/General_paresis_of_the_insane",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Syphilis",
    "human_readable": "The subject of General paresis of the insane is Syphilis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9203284382820129,
            "question": "Is there a link between syphilis and General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8443165421485901,
            "question": "What disease is the subject of General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8349044919013977,
            "question": "What is General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7187826633453369,
            "question": "What medical condition causes General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6949833035469055,
            "question": "What are the symptoms of General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6877315640449524,
            "question": "How is General paresis of the insane treated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6686401963233948,
            "question": "What were the historical understandings of General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5664727091789246,
            "question": "Are there any preventive measures for General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22068022191524506,
            "question": "How does syphilis affect the nervous system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21464954316616058,
            "question": "Can syphilis lead to neurological disorders?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of General paresis of the insane is Syphilis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1731_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does syphilis affect the nervous system?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1731_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any preventive measures for General paresis of the insane?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1731_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the historical understandings of General paresis of the insane?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1731_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1731_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The subject of General paresis of the insane is Syphilis,\" as they describe how general paresis is a result of untreated syphilis and is classified under neurosyphilis."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}